<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Laureta_LabExer4</string>
    <string-array name="company">
        <item>ICBC</item>
        <item>JPMorgan Chase</item>
        <item>China Construction Bank</item>
        <item>Agricultural Bank of China</item>
        <item>Bank of America</item>
        <item>Apple</item>
        <item>Ping An Insurance Group</item>
        <item>Bank of China</item>
        <item>Royal Dutch Shell</item>
        <item>Wells Fargo</item>
        <item>ExxonMobil</item>
        <item>AT&amp;T</item>
        <item>Samsung Electronics</item>
        <item>Citigroup</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="country">
        <item>Country: China</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>
        <item>Country: China</item>
        <item>Country: China</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>
        <item>Country: China</item>
        <item>Country: China</item>
        <item>Country: Netherlands</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>
        <item>Country: South Korea</item>
        <item>Country: United States</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="industry">
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Regional Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Computer Hardware</item>
        <item>Industry: Diversified Insurance</item>
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Oil and Gas Operations</item>
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
        <item>Industry: Oil and Gas Operations</item>
        <item>Industry: Telecommunications Services</item>
        <item>Industry: Semiconductors</item>
        <item>Industry: Major Banks</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ceo">
        <item>CEO: Shu Gu</item>
        <item>CEO: Jamie Dimon</item>
        <item>CEO: Wang Zuji</item>
        <item>CEO: Huan Zhao</item>
        <item>CEO: Brian T. Moynihan</item>
        <item>CEO: Tim Cook</item>
        <item>CEO: Ma Mingzhe</item>
        <item>CEO: Chen Siqing</item>
        <item>CEO: Bernardus Cornelius Margriet van Beurden</item>
        <item>CEO: Timothy Allen Sloan</item>
        <item>CEO: Darren W. W. Woods</item>
        <item>CEO: Randall L. L. Stephenson</item>
        <item>CEO: Hyun-Suk Kim</item>
        <item>CEO: Michael L. Louis Corbat</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="description">
        <item>Industrial and Commercial Bank of China Ltd. engages in the provision of commercial banking and financial services. It operates through the following business...</item>
        <item>JPMorgan Chase and Co. is a financial holding company, which provides financial and investment banking services. It offers a range of investment banking...</item>
        <item>China Construction Bank Corp. engages in the provision of financial and banking services. It operates through the following segments: Corporate Banking...</item>
        <item>Agricultural Bank of China engages in the provision of international commercial banking and financial services. The company operates its business through...</item>
        <item>Bank of America Corp. is a bank and financial holding company, which engages in the provision of banking and nonbank financial services. It operates through...</item>
        <item>Apple, Inc. engages in the design, manufacture, and marketing of mobile communication, media devices, personal computers, and portable digital music players...</item>
        <item>Ping An Insurance (Group) Co. of China Ltd. engages in the provision of financial products and services. The company primarily engages in the business of...</item>
        <item>Bank of China Ltd. engages in the provision of banking and related financial services such as commercial and investment banking, and insurance and investment...</item>
        <item>Royal Dutch Shell Plc engages in the oil and natural gas production. It operates through three segments: Upstream, Downstream, and Corporate. The Upstream...</item>
        <item>Wells Fargo and Co. is a bank holding company that engages in the provision of banking, insurance, investments, mortgage, and consumer and commercial...</item>
        <item>Exxon Mobil Corp. engages in the exploration, development, and distribution of oil, gas, and petroleum products. It operates through the following segments...</item>
        <item>AT&amp;T, Inc. is a holding company, which engages in the provision of telecommunications and digital entertainment services. It operates through the following...</item>
        <item>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. engages in the manufacturing and selling of electronics and computer peripherals. The company operates its business through...</item>
        <item>Citigroup, Inc. is a global financial services holding company specializes in banking and financial solutions. It offers a range of products and services...</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
